supermart.ng 2014-06-26

# Supermart

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy details the kind of information we collect from you, how we use it and how we take steps to secure it. The confidentiality and security of the data we collect from you is of priority to us and it is important you read this Privacy Policy carefully in order to fully understand the terms under which you access and use the Supermart website as well as other Supermart features and services.

**Information We Collect**

In the process of registering for an account on the Supermart website, we may collect some personal identifiable information including but not limited to your name, age, gender, phone number, email address, postal address as well as debit/credit card details. Some of this information may be retained on our website for future reference and use by us while others may be only be used and visible to us during each transaction.

**How We Use Information We Collect**

Supermart collects and uses your personal information to enable us provide services as advertised on our website. This personal information may serve a variety of uses, including notifying you about the status of your order, investigating and resolving complaints/problems, assessing users’ interest in our products and services, notifying you about promotions and offers, customising your shopping experience, minimising fraud and other criminal activity, and for any other reason we deem relevant to your use of Supermart, its services and its website.

At any point in time, you may request to stop receiving any of the information we send you. This request may be granted if it does not impact our ability to effectively fulfil your current as well as future orders.

In order to allow us continually improve our level of service to you, we collect and analyse data about our users' activity on our website. We may also periodically request you to participate in surveys that will give us an indication of your assessment of our level of service, allow us customise your experience on our website, and inform us of ways in which we can improve our service offering.

**Security of Information We Collect**

Supermart makes every attempt to secure your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. Confidential information we receive from you such as debit/credit card details are handled securely and protected through Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data sent from a website to a user’s computer while the user is browsing that website. Cookies are designed to save certain information inputted by a web user on particular web pages that will allow the website recall information such as postal address, phone number, customer name on future visits to that web page.

This provides ease and convenience to a user’s experience by ensuring previously submitted information does not need to be re-entered each time the user is on that web page.

Users have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but your preference can be easily updated in your browser. Opting to decline cookies may restrict users from enjoying the full breadth of Supermart’s website and its associated services and features.
